https://www.centralfloridazoo.org/privacy-policy-2/

DonateThere Is No Zoo Without You
CommemorateYour gift can change our world.
Central Florida Zoo & Botanical Gardens  ›  Privacy Policy
The Central Florida Zoo & Botanical Gardens is concerned about the protection of the privacy of its Web site visitors, our members, and our donors.
We respect your privacy and your choice not to have your personal information shared with other people. We will not sell or exchange any information provided by our Web site visitors, our members or our donors whether the information is obtained online or offline. If at any time you wish to opt-out from communications from the Zoo, please feel free to contact us and we are happy to oblige and stop communication. The information to do so is provided below.
Web Site Information
The Zoo only collects personal contact information (such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses and phone numbers) when users submit it voluntarily. To make our Web site more useful to you, our server automatically collects information when you visit our site, such as, but not limited to, your IP address, date and time of your visit, pages viewed and clickstreams. We will not collect or track information that may identify you personally. Your use of our Web site indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If at any time you wish to opt-out from communications from the Zoo, please feel free to contact us and we are happy to oblige and stop communication.
Mailing Address
We will not sell or exchange your mailing or e-mail address under any circumstance. The Zoo may contact you via mail or e-mail if you have submitted this information voluntarily in accordance with our Privacy Policy. For your knowledge, we periodically send eNewsletters and special event eBlasts updates in reference to our Central Florida Zoo & Botanical Gardens calendar. If at any time you wish to opt-out from communications from the Zoo, please feel free to contact us and we are happy to oblige and stop communication.
Terms of Use
By using this Web site and its content, you agree to be bound by and acknowledge your acceptance of the following Terms of Use and applicable laws. By accessing and browsing this Web site you fully acknowledge and accept the following terms and conditions.
Copyright
Images, text, software, documentation, electronic text and image files, audio and video clips and other materials are the property of the Zoo and will be protected by copyright laws and other restrictions. Furthermore, copyrights and other proprietary rights in the materials on this site may belong to individuals and entities other than the Zoo.
The Zoo expressly prohibits the copying of any protected materials on this Web site, except for the purposes of fair use as defined by copyright law and as described below. This prohibition includes the downloading of site content for commercial use or for use on personal Web sites.
Fair Use
Fair use of copyrighted material includes the use of protected materials for non-commercial educational purposes, such as teaching, scholarship, research, criticism, commentary and news reporting. Users who wish to download or print text and image files from the Zoo’s Web site for such uses must request the Zoo’s express permission by contacting information@centralfloridazoo.org, please include the subject line “Permission for Non-Commercial Use.” Users must cite the author and source for this material as they would material from any printed work and the citation should include the URL <https://www.centralfloridazoo.org.> None of the content may be altered or modified.
Disclaimer
The text, images, and content on this Web site are provided “as is” without a warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied, including but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular use and/or non-infringement. The Zoo assumes no responsibility, and shall not be liable, for any damage or viruses that may infect your computer equipment or other property on account of your use of the site or your downloading of any text, images or content from the Web site. You acknowledge that if you rely on any information or content on the Web site, you do so solely at your own risk.
Contact
Anyone wishing to use any of the files or images contained on this Web site for publication or any purpose other than fair use as defined by law must request and receive prior permission from the Zoo. The responsibility for determining whether any third-party rights exist and for obtaining all other necessary permissions remains solely with the user and the Zoo will have no responsibility in connection with securing such rights for any materials on the Web site. Any other use, such as, without limitation, the use of an image for a commercial purpose, requires the prior written consent of the Zoo, which may be granted or denied at the Zoo’s sole discretion. The failure by the Zoo to insist upon or enforce strict performance of any provision of the Terms of Use by you or others will not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right of the Zoo or other entities’ rights. All requests to reproduce artwork in any form from the Zoo’s collection must be submitted in writing to:
Central Florida Zoo & Botanical Gardens
RE: Rights and Reproductions
PO Box 470309
Lake Monroe, FL 32747
Policy unanimously approved by the Central Florida Zoological Society, Inc. Board of Directors, August 16, 2012.
News
Holiday Hours
Read More
FPL partnership provides upgrades to EV charging statio...
Read More
Central Florida Zoo offers new single-day admission dis...
Read More
x
Thanks for signing up!
Subscribe to Our Newsletter
Sign up to get interesting news and updates delivered to your inbox.
Sign Up
By submitting this form, you are granting: Central Florida Zoo & Botanical Gardens, 3755 W. Seminole Blvd. Sanford, Florida, 32771, United States, permission to email you. You may unsubscribe via the link found at the bottom of every email. (See our Email Privacy Policy for details.) Emails are serviced by Constant Contact.
MENU
Visit
COVID Safety & Modified Operations
Admission & Hours
Annual Pass
Group Rates
Special Discounts
Location
